Started recording.
Okay, so what are we discussing? I forgot.
So okay, fine.
So like I was actually trying to give you
lets say some lines on actually how to
actually go about the go about asking
either actually GLM 5.
2 flash or some other model to help with
finalising the Docmers network. Okay,
Hello.
basically that is a test report.
Yeah.
OK,
the test report actually should start
with actually what is the application
being tested, OK,
whenever like what is the date it is
being tested and so on so forth.
A few attributes, OK, doesn't matter. OK,
we will actually ask actually the models
Mhm.
to like actually give us some idea about
actually what and all should be tested.
It doesn't have to be exhaustive,
but actually we can start with something.
Yeah.
It could either be front matter or it
could be simple table.
Okay, that is actually,
that should be the starting thing.
After that,
actually it should be able to actually
come up with actually some sort of
repeatable grouping. Okay,
it could be sections,
subsections and so on and so forth,
which actually it should actually make
what is it which it should actually do
for and give me a minute every move it
makes.
OK,
it should be able to take a screenshot,
it should be able to write some text to
text for people to understand it.
This is the screen,
I am going to do this or something like
that. OK,
and we don't have to invent this.
Yeah.
I am pretty much sure there is actually
some sort of at least informal document.
OK,
maybe like a there could be defractor
standards in the sense actually people
might be doing it out of habit.
Okay,
you can actually ask for actually such a
report. Okay,
this actually the report actually the
purpose of the report is actually twofold.
One is actually the obvious thing is
Yeah.
actually we will be using that as a
evidence that actually the task is done
correctly. Okay, apart from that,
like asking for the evidence makes the
model to like align with actually what we
want faster.
It can simply claim something without
doing it.
It cannot simply say like I played
actually 10 levels and resolved 10 levels
without actually producing the
screenshots.
So this will ensure that actually the
model is actually aligned with actually
whatever we are trying to do too. OK,
this is actually the run data, OK.
And apart from this run data,
it should be creating the other documents
like documents or data that we already
discussed.
Which are actually the issues or points
of interest which it has to rise to the
human.
So the red document actually is something
that you might never see or you might
actually see when actually you want to
like get something like lets say it says
an issue. Basically,
lets say like it says like in the like
red document,
lets say it says this is level 10, OK,
I have actually cleared one board and
actually I am getting into the second
board.
And in the second board,
actually I am like,
I don't think the lets say problem is
solvable. So I am stopping here.
Then it actually goes to it actually goes
back,
it tries to actually start the next level
and the test itself stops.
Mhm.
When you come back,
it should actually have recorded a
separate fact that actually this is the
point of interest basically. like.
It is not able to proceed as usual.
Okay, and actually like in the document,
it should actually link to the sub
section of the run document in the second
document.
The second document is just point of
interest. Okay,
it says actually this is the like a
section in the run document that is that
Alright.
is actually this particular problem or
this particular quid car actually
something else.
Yeah.
OK,
generally actually you will not be
looking at the end document,
you will be only looking at the point of
end document. Basically,
that is a like a important thing that we
have to notice.
Yeah, I'm listening.
OK,
once like in the important things to
notice it can actually link the section
from the run document itself instead of
actually adding actually the same content
once again.
OK,
and actually from the point of interest
you actually when you ask it to actually
classify it as a bug, OK,
Okay.
it should be adding it to lets say like a
bug document or bug database separately.
For certain, lets go with empty files.
Right.
And actually that will be like an input
for the coding agent that actually we
will have to fix the bug.
Yeah.
Okay, give me one minute, bye.
And apart from this,
like you should be able to give it
actually the permanent memory.
Let us say there is a point of interest
to say actually I am trying to actually
split this actually tile into 2I am not
able to split it. Okay, in the case,
let us say like in that case,
let us say like we know that actually
like the tile is not splitable.
Give me one minute.
Give me one minute, bro.
Yeah.
Mein open zuru.
Yeah.
So what were you discussing on?
So that is a 3rd document that actually,
whenever you say,
it should be able to actually create a
list, add an entry to the memory document,
and this memory document actually is part
Okay.
of the context it should have when it
starts the testing.
So this again the memory document could
be from the POEs themselves or it could
be like some random instructions too. Hey,
don't do this, don't do that,
and so on and so forth.
Mhm.
So like a 3 document, 4 documents,
the run document, the POE document,
the box document, and the KB document,
knowledge document.
Hello.
You can change the names later as of now
we can have some names,
you can change the names later or like
like the run document is actually created
when it actually when it explodes the
application OK either on its own or
Mhm.
actually this as of now lets assume that
actually it is only doing the exploration
part the fixed test actually like we will
go separately the fixed test.
The only difference is actually it will
not actually have a open ended
exploration.
Do you have a run book basically saying
that, hey,
Okay.
execute these things first actually these
4 levels, okay, like in that case,
Yeah.
actually it will actually start with that
instead of empty context,
and then it will try to lets say like
create the run document for that
particular run. Okay,
first is actually the test cases,
Yeah.
the second thing is run.
The 3rd thing is actually point of
interest which actually might actually
link back to run,
and actually the 4th thing is actually
like the bugs document or the issues
document, however you want to call it.
And the 5th thing is what is this
knowledge base?
This actually we should actually try
either with actually like this.
Yeah.
I believe actually we can try both with
actually we can actually start with
actually like economies.
Or plot, whatever you think is conducive,
and I am pretty much sure this will work
Okay.
as is in the other agent too.
Yeah.
So I believe actually we are actually
putting too much into this on the tool.
I don't think actually that's the problem
at the end of it.
Yeah.
It is the hardness that is control by
moral.
Yeah.
So there may maybe some capability
difference,
but I don't think actually it is so like
many of the things we do is it by it
should actually probably work to open
code loop.
Thank you.
So there might be some differences,
but it is not a lot.
Yeah.
So let us try to do one thing.
You actually pick up actually one thing
instead of trying to actually explorer,
actually like some tool in an abstract
fashion,
we try to explorer the tool in the light
Yeah.
of.
Achieving this particular thing.
Yeah.
And I would recommend you to start with
the like if I don't,
I wouldn't recommend you to start with
the test case document, okay,
though like that actually comes as the
first item. Generally,
Yeah.
we'll actually go for it last.
We'll actually start with the run
Hello.
document and then issues, sorry,
run point of interest issues and then
knowledge base or memory,
however you want to call it.
Okay.
Unlike this profiles is that and other
things,
you can worry later if actually
automation is needed.
Okay.
Like if actually profiles are not there,
no,
we will create a new like Linux user
altogether and we have a separate claw
Hello.
One.
for it.
So let's forget about the integrity
integrity difference between claw and
Hermes.
We will actually try to have something
that actually helps us test stuff.
Yeah.
Okay, what is why?
Okay, I'll stop the recording.
Yeah.